coachingsuccessapp.com 2013-12-26

# 

**Professional Marketing International – Privacy Policy.**

Professional Marketing International (“PMI”) provides educational products and training.  Your privacy is very important to us.  As you use our education products and services, we want you to be clear how we’re using the personal information you provide to the Company and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or would like to revise any of your information, please feel free to write to us at Privacy Matters, c/o PMI, 3049 N. Executive Parkway, Lehi, Utah 84043.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it;
  * How we use that information;
  * The choices we offer, including how to limit the information we share with others; and
  * The security, integrity, and confidentiality of the data.

**Information We Collect**

We collect information in order to provide our students with the best educational products and training. We collect only information that our students voluntarily give to the Company.  When you chose to attend one of our educational events, you may fill out forms.  When you do this, you provide the Company personal information, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit card, checking account, personal financial information, business partner information, and other information.

**How We Use Information We Collect**

We use the information our students voluntarily give to the Company to provide, maintain, protect and improve our educational products and training services, and to develop new materials.  We also use this information to offer our students specifically tailored educational products and services – like giving our students information regarding the most relevant educational and training materials to help them reach their goals.

**Information We Share**

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Company unless one of the following circumstances apply:

  * **For Everyday Business Purposes**

This information will be used by the Company to process our students’ transactions, maintain their accounts, and to respond to court orders and legal investigations (as required by law).

  * **For External Processing**

We provide information to our affiliates or other trusted business partners to process the information on our behalf in order to fulfill student orders and requests – based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  * **For Legal Reasons**

We will share information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of our Company if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
    * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of the Company, our students or the public as required or permitted by law.

  * **For Marketing from Other Companies**

 We will share personal information with our partners, affiliates or other trusted businesses to market relevant educational products and services – including telephone solicitations.  The trusted partners are bound by confidentiality agreements, and don’t have any independent right to share your personal information.  Students have the express right to limit (or eliminate) the sharing of information using the opt-out procedure described below.  Also, please write to us to obtain a list of our trusted partners.

**Limit the Information We Share – Opt Out**

You can opt out of the use of your information for marketing by other companies by writing a letter to the Company requesting to opt out and sending it to the Company.  Please feel free to contact through our website, by phone at 800-860-8068, or write to us at Privacy Matters, c/o PMI, 3049 N. Executive Parkway, Lehi, Utah 84043.

**Information Security**

We work hard to protect our students and our Company from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold.  Specifically:

  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to our systems, and to ensure the confidentiality and integrity of the data collected;
  * We restrict access to personal information to Company employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for the Company, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Application and Enforcement**

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the educational products and services offered by the Company and its affiliates or other trusted business partners.  Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or services from unrelated, third-party vendors.  Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who are not related to the Company.

The Company regularly reviews our internal compliance with our Privacy Policy.  The Company also adheres to several internal safeguards related to the information we collect.  When the Company receives formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up.  We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our students directly.

**Changes in the Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time.  We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy at our discretion and without notice.  We will post any privacy policy changes on this page.

Rating: 0.0/ **10** (0 votes cast)
